[](javascript:void(0);)

Privacy Policy
==============

**Introduction**
================

Last Updated (January 11, 2022)

Eldamar Studio is committed to protecting and respecting the privacy of your personal information. This Privacy Policy gives information on how Eldamar Studio (“Company“, “we”, “us”, or “our”) protects your privacy when you use [https://www.eldamar-studio.com](https://www.eldamar-studio.com/) Site as well as any other media form, media channel, mobile Site or mobile application related, linked, or otherwise connected thereto (collectively, the “Site”). 

This Privacy Policy describes the information, both personal and non-personal, that we may collect from you, the purpose for collecting it, how we use it, and who we may share it with and under what circumstance we may share it. This Policy also describes the choices you can make about our collection, use, and disclosure of your information. Eldamar Studio will not collect, use, or disclose your personal information other than as described within this Policy.

We take the protection of your personal information very seriously and will process your personal data fairly, transparently, and lawfully. By accessing or using our Service, you acknowledge that you have read, understood, and agree to our policies as described in this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use. If you do not agree to your information being used as stated in this Privacy Policy, you must stop using the Site.

**Information We Collect From You**

In the course of using the Site services, we will collect or receive certain types of information. By using this Site, you authorize us to collect and/or receive such information. We collect information through different sources as listed below:

**Information You Provide to Us**

You may provide personal information and non-personal information in the course of using our Site. In the scope of this Privacy Policy, personal information means any information about an individual from which that individual can be used to directly identify an individual and non-personal information is any information that cannot be used to directly identify an individual. The information you provide to us includes but is not limited to: your name, workspace name, email address, password, and payment information. This information is collected when you:

* Register an account with us;
* Send us an email;
* Subscribe to our newsletter;
* Purchase a product from us;
* Respond to surveys or questionnaires;
* Information you provide by other means. 

**Information from Third Parties**

We may collect personal information and non-personal information about you from third parties who we have a business relationship with.

**Automatically Collected Information**
---------------------------------------

In addition to the information listed above, we may automatically collect non-personal information from you using a variety of technologies. Examples include IP address, interaction with the Website, usage information, location, type of browser, operating system, your search terms or search queries, internet service providers, and device information. The purpose of collecting non-personal information is to better how you use our Website and its functionalities and how we can improve your browsing experience on our Website.

**How We Use Your Information**
===============================

We use your information for any of the following reasons:

**Contract Administration:** We use your personal information to process your billing information and associated payments. We also use it to communicate with you in the event of a legal proceeding.

**Access and communication on our Site:** We use your information to contact you on our Site for announcements including site updates or to respond to comments, questions, or requests through our Customer Support.

**Website Use:** Website Use: We may use your personal information to better understand your needs and interests as it relates to the Website and help improve the Website for a better browsing experience.

**Fraud Prevention:** We use your personal information for the detection and prevention of fraud or other criminal activities. 

**Shared With Third Parties:** We may share your personal information with affiliated companies to enable them to perform specific services for us. 

**Direct Marketing**: We may use your personal information to contact you to notify you of new offers and services that may be of interest to you.

We also use your information to run background checks and track which demographic is utilizing the platform the most in order to improve our services.

In addition to the purposes set above, please be informed that we may share your information in the circumstance of legal disputes as regards our privacy policies. We may also use it to perform functions as otherwise described at the point of collection of such information. 

**Disclosure of Your Information**
==================================

We may disclose the personal information collected from you on the Site to our affiliates, partners, and other third parties as described below. 

**Third-Party Agents**
----------------------

We share your information with some third-party agents, affiliates, and service providers perform functions on our behalf, including but not limited to: content management, hosting, marketing, analytics, customer service, fraud protection, content syndication, and technical integration. 

These companies may have access to the personal information we collect if needed to perform their function. In the event that such access is required, these third parties will be contractually obligated to maintain the confidentiality and security of that personal information. They are prohibited from selling, using, or distributing this data in any way other than to provide the requested services. 

**Successors**

Eldamar Studio may be involved in mergers, acquisitions, or bankruptcy while providing the Site. In such events, personal information may be part of the transferred assets to the entities acquiring all or part of our assets or another entity with which we have merged. Under such circumstances, we will indulge the acquiring party to follow the terms and practices described in this Privacy Policy. However, once information has been transferred, we cannot promise that the acquiring party will treat your information the same as described in this Privacy Policy. There may be a change in privacy rights. 

**Law Enforcement, Legal Process, and Emergency Situations**
------------------------------------------------------------

We may disclose personal information if required by law to do so or on the good-faith belief that such disclosure is necessary to;

* Protect against legal liability;
* Comply with legal process served on us or our Site or to conform with applicable law;
* Protect and defend our rights or property, our Users, and/or the Site; or
* Act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of us, the Users, or the public.

**Use of Non-Personal Information**
===================================

We may disclose your non-personal information in a manner that we deem appropriate. We may disclose your non-personal information to third parties to help us analyze and determine the behavioral pattern of our Users and from that information, determine how we can further improve our Website. We may also disclose non-personal information to our service providers and other third parties about how our Users collectively use the Website.

**Security of Your Information** 

We care about the security of your personal information and we take adequate security steps to ensure that we protect such information. Part of our security measures means that we may occasionally request proof of identity before we disclose your personal information to you. 

We encode your information using Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption technology when you place an order using the Site. While we have employed security technologies and procedures to assist safeguarding your personal information, the Internet cannot be guaranteed to be 100% secure, and we, therefore, cannot guarantee the total security of any information you provide to us. Please bear this in mind when disclosing any Personal Information. In case any information under our control gets compromised, we will take appropriate steps to investigate the situation and notify the appropriate individuals whose information may have been compromised. We would also take other steps in accordance with applicable laws and regulations.

**How We Store Your Information**

Please be informed that by submitting your personal information to us through the Site, you agree that we may transfer, store, and process your personal information in the Netherlands. Although this Site is accessible around the world, the use of this Site is governed in accordance with the laws of Ukraine. We make no representations that the Site is operated or governed in accordance with the laws of any other state or country. 

When you visit the Site, your connection will be through and to servers located in the Netherlands. All information you receive from us will be generated from servers in the Netherlands, and all information you provide will be maintained on web servers stationed in the Netherlands. When you use the Site or submit information to us, you consent to the transfer of information to the facilities and servers located in the Netherlands.

**Retention of Your Information**

We retain personal information about you no longer than is necessary to complete the purpose for which it was collected. We may retain your information for a longer period of time if it is required by applicable law. Personal information shared by you for direct marketing purposes will be stored with us until you opt-out of receiving marketing communications or you make a request to our Customer Support at [radkevychtetiana@gmail.com](mailto:radkevychtetiana@gmail.com) to opt-out.

**Marketing Communications**

We may from time to time send you marketing communications via email about products or services that may be of interest to you. We are aware that no one likes receiving unsolicited emails. As such, you will only receive marketing communications from us if you opt-in to receive them from us. If you decide at any point in time that you no longer want to receive our marketing communications, you can opt-out at any time by opening any marketing email we send to you and clicking on the “Unsubscribe” link or send us an email at [radkevychtetiana@gmail.com](mailto:radkevychtetiana@gmail.com) with a request to unsubscribe.

**Children’s Information**

We understand the importance of children’s privacy and safety. This Site is not intended for children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly or intentionally collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If you are under 13 years of age and you use our Site, please stop immediately.

If you have reason to believe that a child under the age of 13 has provided personal information to our Site, please contact our Customer Support at [radkevychtetiana@gmail.com](mailto:radkevychtetiana@gmail.com), and upon verification, we will take appropriate steps to delete the personal information from our database.

**Your Data Protection Rights**

We would like to make sure you are fully aware of all of your data protection rights and how you can exercise them.

Every user is entitled to the following:

**The right of access** – You have the right to request a free copy of any and all personal information we hold on you.

**The right to rectification** – You have the right to request that we correct any personal information about you that you believe is inaccurate. You may be required to give evidence to show that the personal information is inaccurate. You also have the right to request the completion of personal information that you believe is incomplete. You may be required to give evidence to show that the personal information is inaccurate.

**Your right to erasure** – You have the right to request that we erase your personal information that we may have in our databases and systems. 

**Right to data portability** – You have the right to ask us to electronically move, copy or transfer the personal information we have of you in a machine-readable format.

**The right to restrict processing** – You have the right to request that we restrict the processing of your personal information, under certain conditions.

**The right to withdraw consent**– You have the right to withdraw your previously given consent to process your personal information at any time and for any reason. 

Please be informed that it is not always possible to totally delete all your personal information from our systems without some residual backup in order to comply with legal obligations, resolve disputes, or for other legitimate reasons.

In the event that we are not able to remove your personal information, we will endeavor to let you know why we are unable to do so. We process all requests within one month of receiving such requests. Such requests should be submitted to [radkevychtetiana@gmail.com](mailto:hello@brandcandie.com). For verification purposes, we will only respond to requests sent from the email address that you provided when you registered for an account with us on the Site.

**Third Party Applications and Links to Other Sites**

Our Site may contain links to third-party Sites that are not affiliated or controlled by us. By accessing a third-party Site through our Site, you acknowledge that you know that the information you provide to these third-party Sites is not covered by our Privacy Policy and you release us from any responsibility for the conduct of these third-party Sites.

Before visiting and providing information on these third-party Sites, you are advised to review their privacy policies and practices of the third-party responsible for the Site before purchasing a product from them, making use of their services, or submitting any information.

**Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies**

Cookies are small text files that contain a small amount of information that is stored on a user’s computer and provided by the visitor’s browser to the Site every time a User revisits the Site. We automatically collect certain types of usage data when you visit our Site using cookies. Cookies allow you to log in faster and improve your navigation through the Site. We may collect anonymous information from your browser such as your IP address, device information, and browser type.

Below are some of the types of cookies that may be used on our Site:

**Analytics Cookies**

Analytics cookies monitor how users reached and interact with the Site. These cookies let us learn which features on the Site are works best for the users and which features can be improved upon. 

**Strictly Necessary Cookies**

These are cookies necessary for the proper functioning of the Site without which the Site won’t work properly or be able to provide certain features and functionalities. Some of these cookies may be manually disabled in your browser but disabling may affect the functionality of the Site.

**Personalization Cookies**
---------------------------

Personalization cookies are cookies used to identify repeat visitors on our Website. We use these cookies to keep a record of the pages you have visited, your browsing history, and your settings and preferences each time you visit the Website.  

We may also make use of web beacons to anonymously track usage patterns of our Users. Web beacons are electronic files hosted on the Website that controls usage. Web beacons allow for more accurate analysis and improvement of our Website Services.

**Security Cookies**

Security cookies help identify and prevent security risks. We use these cookies to protect user data from malicious parties and authenticate users.  

**Corrections**

In the event that we believe that the personal information we hold about you is inaccurate, incomplete, out-of-date, or misleading, we will take reasonable measure to correct the information.

You have the right to request correction of your personal information if you believe that the personal information that we hold about you is incorrect. You can make this request by contacting us at [radkevychtetiana@gmail.com](mailto:hello@brandcandie.com). In the event that we do not agree with the requested correction, we reserve the right to refuse to alter your personal information.

**Changes to This Privacy Policy**

We may from time to time modify the terms in this Privacy Policy. We will inform you of any changes to this Privacy Policy by updating the Last Updated at the top of the page. We hereby advise you to occasionally review this Privacy Policy to remain informed of any changes to our policies. When the changes are determined as more material, we will attempt to contact you or put a notice about the change of policy on the Site.

**Contact Us**

If you have any inquiries or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy or you would like to exercise one of your data protection rights, please contact us at  

**info@eldamar-studio.com**

Eldamar Studio Inc.

5005 Dalhousie Dr NW Unit 175 #1279  
Calgary, AB, T3A 5R8

Canada

**Eldamar Studio** offers a huge collection of best quality Photoshop Overlays, LUTs, Lightroom Presets, VFX Assets, GameDev Assets, and many other digital products.

##### BROWSE CATEGORIES

##### USEFUL LINKS

##### INFORMATION

COPYRIGHT 2024 **ELDAMAR STUDIO** © ALL RIGHTS RESERVED

  Search

Shopping cart

### Sign in

Username or email address \* 

Password \* 

  Log in

[Lost your password?](https://eldamar-studio.com/my-account/lost-password/)  Remember me

No account yet?

We use cookies to improve your experience on our website. By browsing this website, you agree to our use of cookies.

  Search

Start typing to see products you are looking for.
